Guide to the James M. Foster papers, 1971-1990
Foster, James M. papers, 1971-1990
- Series II. Subject Files
  - Health
    - 1987 Budget (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Conference Commission - Public Health (Box 13, Folder 47-49)
    - Rules of Order (Box 13, Folder 50-51)
    - Federal Funding 1986 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Forensics (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - MBO (Management-by-Objectives) (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Department of Public Health (DPH)/Mental Health (Box 13, Folder 55-56)
    - Toxic Control (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence Summaries (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Veterans (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
    - Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Regionalization (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Ambulance Destination Policy (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Sonoma County (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence Received (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Orange County (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Marin County (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Contra Costa County (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Alameda County (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Physicians' Assistants (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Foster Speech (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - "Public Health and AIDS" (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - PWA (People with AIDS) Organizations (Box 14, Folder 17-18)
    - Safety Issues (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Medicaid (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Ad Campaign/Testing (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Frank Young/FDA (Food and Drug Administration) (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Activists vs. Lymphomed (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Trials (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Newport Pharmaceuticals (Isoprinosine) (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Financial Reports (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Tokos Medical Corporation (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Clinical Partners (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Clinical Partners Invoices (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - National Medical Care (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Clinical Partners Expenses (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Drug Reimbursement Policy (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Protocare (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Production Specialties (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Caremark Reports (Box 14, Folder 35-36)
      - Caremark Contract/Proposal (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Caremark Resource Manual (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Caremark Homecare 1990 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Foster Speeches (Box 14, Folder 40-44)
    - Speech Background Material (Box 14, Folder 45-48)
    - Day Care (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - City and County Officers (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Gay Lists (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - San Francisco Department of Public Health Lists (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Press Lists (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Morrison List (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - San Francisco General Hospital List (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Department of Public Health (DPH)
      - DPH - Authority and Rules of Order (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - DPH - Budget (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - DPH - Travel Letters (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - DPH - Directors' Reports (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
      - DPH - Substance Abuse (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - DPH - Substance Abuse (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - DPH - Laguna Honda JCC (Joint Conference Committee) (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - DPH - San Francisco General Hospital JCC (Joint Conference Committee) (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - DPH - Public Health JCC (Joint Conference Committee) (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - DPH - Laguna Honda Minutes (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - DPH - Mental Health (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - DPH - Homeless (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - DPH - Emergency Services (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - DPH - Public Health Hospital (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Tom Waddell Clinic (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Hospice (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
    - Tenderloin AIDS Network (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - AIDS Service Providers (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Continuum (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Kaiser Permanente (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - 18th Street Services (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Operation Concern (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Shanti (Box 15, Folder 19-21)
    - National Association of People With AIDS (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Episcopal AIDS Task Force (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Domestic Partners (Box 15, Folder 33-34)
    - BETA (Bulletin of Experimental Treatment of AIDS) Newsletter (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Ireland (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - HMSS Management, Inc. Contract and Proposal, HMSS - "Specializing in Home Intravenous Therapies" (Box 15, Folder 37-40)
    - Waxman Amendments (Box 15, Folder 41-44)
    - Stark Bill (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Geto and DeMilly/Fisher (Public Relations) (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Contract and Conflict of Interest (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Weiss Committee (Box 15, Folder 48-49)
    - FDA Hearing (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - New York Times Editorial Response (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Foster Response Letters (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Kennedy committee - Lymphomed (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Methadone Clinics - Lymphomed (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Press Clippings - Lymphomed (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous background material, including numerous reports, findings, newsletters and other publications, and booklets pertaining mainly to AIDS health care issues (Box 16-17)
- Series III. Audiocassettes
  - Audiocassettes (Box 9)